kin.today 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Kin Calendar

_Wednesday September 07 2016  
Kin Calendar, a project by Benoit Person and Yann Person _

This Privacy Policy describes what data we collect and process when you use the Kin website and iOS applications (“Service”). The Service includes a software application users download to a device or browser, an interactive website and a service that processes data on our servers. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please return to it whenever you want to obtain information about your privacy options.

## Data We Process.

### Account Credentials.

We collect and process your account credentials to provide you the Service. Your account credentials may include the username and password you created when signing up for the Service, or your Facebook, Google or other identity that you used to sign up, which may include the name you provided to that service. If you connect your account to a third party service, we store your authentication token to enable this access. Kin does not use your account credentials for any other purpose.

### Calendar Data.

We collect and process your calendar data. Calendar data includes your schedule, the content of your calendar entries, and associated information from the local calendar on your device as well as third-party sites, applications and services. Your calendar data may contain meetings, appointments, birthdays, messages, contact information and other attachments. Kin uses this information solely to provide you the Service.

### Email Address.

We collect and process your email address to provide you the Service, carry out transactions you authorize and communicate with you. For example, we use your email address to request feedback or provide updates and notifications regarding the Service. You may control promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out of promotional messages, you may still receive emails from us relating to your account and the Service (e.g., relating to product updates, etc.). These account communications are part of the Service, and account holders cannot opt out of receiving these account communications.

### Device Information.

When you download or use one of our applications or extensions, we will collect and process certain information about your device, such as your device type, operating system and version, mobile network or other Internet service provider information, unique device IDs and IP address. We use this information to personalize your experience and provide and improve our Service.

### Log Data.

Like most websites, we log information about your use of the Service, including the type of browser or device you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Service. We use this information to personalize your experience and provide and improve our Service.

### Usage Information.

We may use cookies, device identifiers and other technologies to collect and process information about your use of the Service. We use this information to personalize your experience and provide and improve our Service.

### Support.

If you encounter problems with the Service, you may contact us for technical support by emailing [hello@kin.today](mailto:hello@kin.today). We will retain communications related to support issues in order to provide and improve the Service.

### Disclosure of Data.

We may disclose information about you in the following circumstances: 

  * If you direct or authorize the disclosure.
  * As necessary to provide the Service, including sharing information with third parties who store or manage your calendars and related information.
  * If we believe in good faith that we must disclose information: to protect the rights or property of our company or other users, including to prevent fraud or to enforce our agreements or policies governing your use of the Service; or, if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary, to protect the personal safety of our personnel, users, or the public.
  * If we sell or reorganize all or part of our business, we may disclose user information to a third party who acquires us or all or part of our assets, as permitted by law.
  * To vendors, consultants and other service providers as necessary to provide services for us (such as customer support, email marketing, and technical infrastructure services).
  * We also share aggregated statistical information with our analytics partners, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

Finally, we may access, disclose and preserve your personal information, including your private content (such as the content of your calendar events, meetings, contacts or other private communications or files), when we have a good faith belief that doing so is necessary to: 

  * comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process from competent authorities, including from law enforcement or other government agencies;
  * protect our customers, for example to prevent spam or attempts to defraud users of the Service, or to help prevent the loss of life or serious injury;
  * operate and maintain the security of the Service, including to prevent or stop an attack on our computer systems or networks; or
  * protect our rights or property, including enforcing the terms governing the use of the Service – however, if we receive information indicating that someone is using the Service to traffic in our stolen intellectual or physical property, we will not inspect a customer’s private content ourselves, but we may refer the matter to law enforcement.
  * Please note that the Service may include links to or from sites or services of third parties that have privacy practices different from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites or services, your information is governed by the privacy policies of those third parties. This includes Calendar Data that is synced with third-party services.

### Security.

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems that have limited access and are in controlled facilities, and any information sent or received from third party services linked to your account is transmitted via a secure connection.

### Deleting Your Data.

You can deactivate your account in Settings. When you deactivate your account, we will delete your information as soon as reasonably practical, and will only retain information as required by law. Deletion of any information from third party services that you connect to the Service is managed through that third party service, and governed by their terms of use and privacy policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We may modify and revise our Privacy Policy from time to time. When we post changes to our Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of the statement. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on the Service or by sending you an email or other notification.

## How to Contact Us.

If you need more information, please contact us at [hello@kin.today](mailto:hello@kin.today).
